[
    {
        "question": "1 + 0",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 0",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "1 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 0",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 0",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 1",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 1",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 * 1",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 0",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 0",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 1",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 1",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 1",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 2",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 2",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "3 * 2",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 0",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 0",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 1",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 1",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 1",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 2",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 2",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 2",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 3",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 3",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "4 * 3",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 0",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 0",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 1",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 1",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 1",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 2",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 2",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 2",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 3",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 3",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 3",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 4",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 4",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "5 * 4",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 0",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 0",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 1",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 1",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 1",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 2",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 2",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 2",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 3",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 3",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 3",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 4",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 4",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 4",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 5",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 5",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "6 * 5",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 0",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 0",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 1",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 1",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 1",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 2",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 2",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 2",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 3",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 3",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 3",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 4",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 4",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 4",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 5",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 5",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 5",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 6",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 6",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "7 * 6",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 0",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 0",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 1",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 1",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 1",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 2",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 2",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 2",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 3",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 3",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 3",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 4",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 4",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 4",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 5",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 5",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 5",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 6",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 6",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 6",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 7",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 7",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "8 * 7",
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 0",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 0",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 1",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 1",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 1",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 2",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 2",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 2",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 3",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 3",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 3",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 4",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 4",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 4",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 5",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 5",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 5",
        "answer": 45
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 6",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 6",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 6",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 7",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 7",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 7",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 8",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 8",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "9 * 8",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 0",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 0",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 1",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 1",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 1",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 2",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 2",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 2",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 3",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 3",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 3",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 4",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 4",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 4",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 5",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 5",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 5",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 6",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 6",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 6",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 7",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 7",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 7",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 8",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 8",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 8",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 9",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 9",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10 * 9",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 0",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 0",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 1",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 1",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 1",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 2",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 2",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 2",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 3",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 3",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 3",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 4",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 4",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 4",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 5",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 5",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 5",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 6",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 6",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 6",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 7",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 7",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 7",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 8",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 8",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 8",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 9",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 9",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 9",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 10",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 10",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "11 * 10",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 0",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 0",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 1",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 1",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 1",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 2",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 2",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 2",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 3",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 3",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 3",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 4",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 4",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 4",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 5",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 5",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 5",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 6",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 6",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 6",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 7",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 7",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 7",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 8",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 8",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 8",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 9",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 9",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 9",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 10",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 10",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 10",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 11",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 11",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "12 * 11",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 0",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 0",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 1",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 1",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 1",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 2",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 2",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 2",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 3",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 3",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 3",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 4",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 4",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 4",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 5",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 5",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 5",
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 6",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 6",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 6",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 7",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 7",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 7",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 8",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 8",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 8",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 9",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 9",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 9",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 10",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 10",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 10",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 11",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 11",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 11",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 12",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 12",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "13 * 12",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 0",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 0",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 1",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 1",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 1",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 2",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 2",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 2",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 3",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 3",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 3",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 4",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 4",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 4",
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 5",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 5",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 5",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 6",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 6",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 6",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 7",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 7",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 7",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 8",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 8",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 8",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 9",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 9",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 9",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 10",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 10",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 10",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 11",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 11",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 11",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 12",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 12",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 12",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 13",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 13",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "14 * 13",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 0",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 0",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 1",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 1",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 1",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 2",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 2",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 2",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 3",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 3",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 3",
        "answer": 45
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 4",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 4",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 4",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 5",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 5",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 5",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 6",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 6",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 6",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 7",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 7",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 7",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 8",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 8",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 8",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 9",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 9",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 9",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 10",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 10",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 10",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 11",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 11",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 11",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 12",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 12",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 12",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 13",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 13",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 13",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 14",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 14",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "15 * 14",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 0",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 0",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 1",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 1",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 1",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 2",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 2",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 2",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 3",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 3",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 3",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 4",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 4",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 4",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 5",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 5",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 5",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 6",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 6",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 6",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 7",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 7",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 7",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 8",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 8",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 8",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 9",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 9",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 9",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 10",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 10",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 10",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 11",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 11",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 11",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 12",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 12",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 12",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 13",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 13",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 13",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 14",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 14",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 14",
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 15",
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 15",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "16 * 15",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 0",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 0",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 1",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 1",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 1",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 2",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 2",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 2",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 3",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 3",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 3",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 4",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 4",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 4",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 5",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 5",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 5",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 6",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 6",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 6",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 7",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 7",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 7",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 8",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 8",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 8",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 9",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 9",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 9",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 10",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 10",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 10",
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 11",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 11",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 11",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 12",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 12",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 12",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 13",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 13",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 13",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 14",
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 14",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 14",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 15",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 15",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 15",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 16",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 16",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "17 * 16",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 0",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 0",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 0",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 1",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 1",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 1",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 2",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 2",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 2",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 3",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 3",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 3",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 4",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 4",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 4",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 5",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 5",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 5",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 6",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 6",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 6",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 7",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 7",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 7",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 8",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 8",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 8",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 9",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 9",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 9",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 10",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 10",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 10",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 11",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 11",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 11",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 12",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 12",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 12",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 13",
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 13",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 13",
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 14",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 14",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 14",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 15",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 15",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 15",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 16",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 16",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 16",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 17",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 17",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "18 * 17",
        "answer": 306
    }
]